# Andrew J Moser Salem, OR

## Dear recruiter/hiring manager:

After researching about your company on google, I am very excited to work with your organization. I know I can bring value to your team due to work ethics instilled in me by my family and my personal beliefs. I believe that I would be a great match based on my extensive experience and skills listed below.

## **Your requirements**

# My qualifications

Ability to create and support documentation experience	Ability to create and support documentation experience
Strong teamwork skills	I have strong teamwork skills working in agile environments
Proven knowledge of the most current security and web development programming languages	Fluent in languages such as Javascript, JQuery, Angular, Ruby, Mongo, HTML, CSS and more
Writing well designed, testable, efficient code by using best software development practices	I am a technical writer at heart and can write, design and test code using the most up to date practices such as DRY code and sudo coding
Creating website layout/user interfaces by using standard HTML/CSS practices	I am fluent in HTML and CSS and can create any website using those languages and various frameworks for styling
Integrating data from various back-end services and databases	Able to use express, rails, mongodb and SQL in setting up and integrating back end to front end communication with databases.
Gather data needed for web design	I have experience writing user stories and taking input for website design criteria and fulfilling those criteria.

# Andrew J Moser Salem, OR

ajmoser80@gmail.com

503-851-1156

www.linkedin.com/in/andrew-moser

#### CUSTOMER FOCUSED SOLUTIONS DEVELOPER

### Improving operations and deliver positive results through customer interaction

Analytical thinking person with extensive experience in customer service. Worked for nationwide and worldwide companies known for awards in customer service. Well known as an innovative thinker. A flexible, approachable leader with excellent problem solving skills and very strong work ethics.

Reliable and punctual Multi-talented and organized

Responsible and mature Excellent customer service

Ethical and hard worker Effective communicator

Quick learner and thinker Overachiever deliverer

#### ACCOMPLISHMENTS

- Graduated from General Assembly in September 2017. During the course I completed at least 5 projects using various developer languages. Link to github profile <a href="https://github.com/Elmanite">https://github.com/Elmanite</a>
- Created a coordinated program for tracking delegated responsibilities for schedules on google calendar at the Trip-Link call center
- Implemented a new financial tracking and notation form for our local collections team at Seterus.
- Awarded the opportunity to perform peer to peer mentoring for T-Mobile, which was to
  evaluate peer agents behaviors in order to improve their performance and quality. As a
  result, one of them even got promoted.
- Earned the highly coveted "Charlie Chip" award for excellent customer service at Fry's Electronics.

 Recognized as a top performer in delinquency management at Seterus several months in a row and promoted to different departments as a result

#### PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

### Seterus / IBM - Salem, OR

June 2015 – August 2017

**Quality Assurance Specialist:** 

Evaluating recorded calls for compliance and quality purposes. Coach co-workers to improve their call taking and Microsoft Office skills.

### Seterus / Aerotek - Salem and Beaverton, OR

November 2014 - June 2015

Contact Strategy Officer:

Managed agent's schedules and worked with multiple departments to monitor call center, operational efficiency. Analyzed reports to assist with call queue forecasting and creating schedules accordingly to ensure phone coverage.

#### Seterus / Aerotek - Salem, OR

August 2013 - November 2014

Delinquency Management Specialist:

Started out as a call agent to help delinquent home-owners by keeping up to date with both company and government policies surrounding the mortgage industry, presenting solution strategies to resolve delinquency and assisting borrowers with financial profiling.

## MV Transportation/Trip-Link Operator - Salem, OR

September 2008 - July 2013

Quality Assurance Specialist:

Started as a call taker taking reservations and moved my way up to scheduler specialist. Managed training for all new hire agents as well as updated training for existing agents. Created and kept up to date manuals on company and state government policies regarding medical transportation and transportation management software.

## Triplett Wellman - Woodburn, OR

September 2006 - December 2007

Carpenter:

Operated heavy machinery including forklifts, scissor lifts, boom man-lift and grade-all forklifts. Also responsible for site demolition, framing, setting concrete forms, finishing concrete and site cleanup.

#### T-Mobile - Salem, OR

August 2000 - September 2006

Customer Service and Retention Representative:

Received calls for customer concerns/questions on billing, technical problems and taking escalated calls. Later promoted to cancellation department to help retain customer loyalty.

## Fry's Electronics – Wilsonville, OR

November 1998 – May 2000

Customer service cashier:

Handled customer purchase transactions, money handling and addressing customer complaints/concerns. Also performed trouble shooting techniques in order to persuade customers to retain purchases. Awarded multiple times for excellent customer service.

## Americold Logistics – Salem, OR

June 1998 – September 1998

Dock labor and driver:

Operated forklifts, electric and manual pallet jacks to load/unload and mark frozen food items to be stored.

#### **EDUCATION**

June - September 2017 - Studied at General Assembly - Web Development Immersive graduate. Link to completed projects profile <a href="https://github.com/Elmanite/Portfolio">https://github.com/Elmanite/Portfolio</a> 1999: Completed coursework at ITT Technical institute in Portland Oregon. 1998: High school diploma from Salem Academy.

#### REFERENCES

Kevin Schmidt - T-mobile, Solution Special Senior Representative Kevin.schmidt@tmobile.com

Vere O'kelly – AVP Contact Strategy at Seterus Inc owned by IBM in the division of Global Process Services delivery vokelle@us.ibm.com

Tiffany Kahle – Quality Assurance manager at Seterus Inc. owned by IBM in the division of Global Process Services delivery.

503-686-7361

Tiffany.Kahle@us.ibm.com